Naji husam mansour

Phone: +962 772157686 Linkedin: Naji mansour Birthday: 11/4/2002

Email:najimansour22@gmail.com Live: jordan - zarqa Nationality: Jordanian

SUMMARY

As a graduated of digital media specialty, and through my experiences, i have the ability to manage social media platforms and digital marketing and public relations work, and have the ability to administrative work and office work.

EDUCATION

02/2021 - 02/2023 Diploma in Digital Media

Al-Balqa Applied University

09/2019 - 09/2020 High school - literary

Al-shamleh for boys

EXPERIENCE

03/2024 - 06/2024 Social media intern

Jordan, Amman

For Ministry of Higher Education and scientific research

- Preparing content for social media platforms(write, design).
- social media platforms Moderator.
- prepare plans for social media platforms.
- Prepare content for websites.
- assisting in public relations work such as event management, printing files, writing reports and memos, archiving and documenting, Reply to letters and correspondence.

10/2022 - 02/2023

Websites editor intern

Jordan, Amman

For Al taj news

- write press news and reports
- searching for information
- social media management

COURSES

Workshop on media and information education

Workshop Making a movie by mobile phone

SKILLS

journalism, social media, Public relations, digital marketing, Communication, Organizational, content writer, Team work, canva, adobe programs, Email managment, data entry, microsoft word microsoft excel, microsoft PowerPoint, office work, administrative

LANGUAGES

Arabic Mother tongue

English very good